zuuzs.com 2013-04-11

# zuuzs.com | Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

## Introduction

zuuzs, LLC (“ _zuuzs_ ” or “we” or “us” or “our”) respects the privacy of its Members (“you” or “Member”) and has developed this “Privacy Policy” to demonstrate its commitment to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect, how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and your choices about such uses and disclosures.  We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using zuuzs.com or services or transacting business with us or our Merchants (as defined in the [Terms of Service](http://www.zuuzs.com/about/terms/) via zuuzs.com. By using zuuzs.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us.

## What Data We Collect and Why

The information we learn from our Members helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping and social experience at zuuzs.com.  We may collect Personal Information that can identify you (“Personal Information”) such as your name and email address as well as other information that does not identify you (“Anonymous Information”).  When you provide Personal Information through zuuzs.com, the information may be sent to servers located across the United States.  Below are the types of information we gather.

  * ### 1\. Information You Provide 

We collect and store any Personal Information you submit to us voluntarily through zuuzs.com or provide to us in some other manner ( _e.g._ , creating/editing your Member profile, information entered in reviews, ratings, postings, comments, and forums). This includes identifying information, such as your name, address, email address, telephone number, and profile picture, and, if you transact business with us, financial information such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information). 

We also may request information about your interests, activities, gender, age, and other demographic information, which we may share with advertisers on an anonymous basis.  If you sign up for surveys or other activities that we make available to you on zuuzs.com, we will collect the information designated along with such activity, which may include your contact information such as your address and phone number.  If you choose to sign up to receive information about products or services that may be of interest to you, we will collect your email address and other related information. 

  * ### 2\. Information From Other Sources

    1. #### A. Cookies and Other Technologies 

We use cookies and other technologies, such as, web beacons (also known as “clear gifs” and “pixel tags”) to recognize you, customize your experience, and serve advertisements.   Cookies are very small files placed on your computer, and they allow us to count the number of visitors to zuuzs.com and distinguish repeat visitors from new visitors. They also allow us to save Member preferences and track Member trends. We rely on cookies for the proper operation of zuuzs.com; therefore if your browser is set to reject all cookies, the website will not function properly and you may lose functionality.  Specifically, we require our Members to have cookies enabled in order to accumulate and receive fundzs ( _i.e._ , cash payments).  We do not link cookies or web beacons to any Personal Information.   We may also enable advertisers and ad servers to promote third-party products and/or services by placing advertisements on zuuzs.com. These advertisers and ad servers may use cookies and/or web beacons to monitor information related to served advertisements. Clicking on such advertisements will direct you to the website of a third-party and the advertiser. This Privacy Policy does not cover the privacy practices of any advertisers or ad servers.

    2. #### B. Information Collected Automatically 

We automatically receive and collect from your internet use information like your IP address, the URLs of websites from which you arrive or leave zuuzs.com, your type of browser and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us, your operating system, your mobile provider, your mobile device, and your ISP. We may use such information to analyze trends, administer the website, prevent fraud, track visitor movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information.  

    3. #### C. Website Activity Information 

We keep track of some of the actions you take on zuuzs.com, such as participating on discussion boards/forums, providing ratings and reviews, inviting friends or indicating you “like” a post/product. When you provide information or content to us, such as, profile pictures, sharing a review or rating, in addition to storing the actual content you uploaded, we might log the fact that you shared it.  Furthermore, any information that is disclosed on discussion boards/forums become public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any Personal Information. 

    4. #### D. Information Collected by Third Parties

We retain information you provide in connection with third party services, which includes Merchants, available through zuuzs.com like surveys and polls or other third party research undertaken with your consent. We may also collect information about you and your friends who use zuuzs.com, from any social network you may have connected from, in order to provide you with a more personalized experience.  We may establish programs with advertising partners and other websites in which they share information with us, such as, ask advertisers to tell us how our Members responded to the ads we showed them (and for comparison purposes, how other Members who didn’t see the ads acted on their website). This data sharing, commonly known as “conversion tracking,” helps us measure our advertising effectiveness and improve the quality of the advertisements you see. We may receive information about whether or not you’ve seen or interacted with certain ads on other websites in order to measure the effectiveness of those ads.  If in any of these cases we receive data that we do not already have, we will within 180 days, stop associating Personal Information received with any particular Member. If we institute these programs, we will only use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

    5. #### E. Information from Other Members 

We may collect information about you from other zuuzs.com Members when interacting on zuuzs.com.

    6. #### F. E-mail Communications 

We require an e-mail address to register on zuuzs.com. We use your e-mail for both transactional ( _e.g._ , order confirmation) and promotional ( _e.g._ , newsletters, new product offerings, special discounts, special third-party offers) purposes. E-mail messages we send you may contain code that enables our database to track your usage of the e-mails, including whether the e-mail was opened and what links (if any) were clicked.  If you send an e-mail to us, or fill out our “Feedback” form, we will collect your e-mail address and the full content of your e-mail, including attached files, and other information you provide. We may use and display your full name and email address when you send an email notification to a friend through zuuzs.com or the social network from which you have connected to zuuzs.com (such as in an invitation, or when sharing your content). Additionally, we use your email address to contact you on behalf of your friends (such as when someone sends you a personal message) or notifications from a social network or other website with whom you have registered to receive such notifications. 

You may indicate your preference to stop receiving further promotional communications.  If you would rather not receive promotional e-mails from us, please see the section below labeled Opt-Out.  We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to zuuzs.com services, such as service announcements and administrative messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. We may also contact you by telephone or text message (including to any wireless number you may provide to us) solely in connection with zuuzs.com services. If you would rather not receive telephone calls or text messages from us, you may change or delete your number from your account preferences page(s), or ask to be removed from our contact list if you receive a call or text message from us. 

We fully comply with the requirements of the U.S. CAN-SPAM Act.  zuuzs.com does not support spamming by our Members and we explicitly prohibit it in our Terms of Service. If you would like to report an incident of spamming, please contact us at contact@zuuzs.com. We will investigate and take suitable action.

    7. #### G. Information About Others 

We encourage you to refer your family, friends, and colleagues to zuuzs.com by sending us their name and email address. We will keep this information in our database, and send that person an e-mail containing your name and inviting them to visit zuuzs.com. This e-mail will also include instructions on how to remove their information from our database. You agree that you will not abuse this feature by entering names and addresses of those who would not be interested in zuuzs.com’s services. 

zuuzs.com provides value to its Member by paying fundzs ( _i.e._ , cash rewards) to our Members. The information we collect ( _e.g._ , name, email address, and physical address) is used to track and send fundzs Members earn.

Additionally, we may use information on the websites you visit or the offers you view on zuuzs.com to select special offers that will be relevant to you. Except at an aggregate level, however, we do not share that information with our partners, advertisers or other third parties.

## How We Use the Information We Collect

We may use information that we collect about you to: 

  1. Deliver the products and services that you have requested.
  2. Enable you to share your information and communicate with other Members.
  3. Manage your account and provide you with customer support.
  4. Enable third-party service providers who work on behalf of or with us to provide some of the services and features of zuuzs.com.
  5. Share your content preferences and other information with the social network with which you have connected to zuuzs.com, along with those companies and persons you have asked us to share your information with.
  6. Perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others.
  7. Communicate with you by email, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us or other third parties.
  8. Develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on zuuzs.com and other websites.
  9. Verify your eligibility to participate on zuuzs.com.
  10. Enforce our [Terms of Service](http://www.zuuzs.com/about/terms/).
  11. Manage our business.
  12. Provide zuuzs.com advertisements to you when you visit other websites.
  13. Perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

From time to time, we may use Member information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in the then-current Privacy Policy.  If our information practices change in the future we will post such changes to zuuzs.com to notify you of these changes. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at zuuzs.com periodically.

We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your Personal Information to any third parties for marketing purposes. 

## Who Sees Your Personal Information

  1. ### 1\. Our Employees

Only a very limited number of zuuzs.com employees ever have access to your Personal Information. This information is used to track and send fundzs you earn.

  2. ### 2\. Our Members

When you use zuuzs.com, certain information you post or provide through zuuzs.com, such as your name, profile, picture, comments, collections and reviews, may be shared with other Members and posted on publicly available portions of zuuzs.com, including without limitation, social media applications and other public forums in which you choose to participate. Please keep in mind that if you choose to disclose Personal Information when posting comments or other information or content through zuuzs.com, this information may become publicly available and may be collected and used by others, including people outside of zuuzs.com. We will not have any obligations with respect to any information that you post to parts of zuuzs.com available to others, and recommend that you use caution when giving out Personal Information to others through social media networks or otherwise.

  3. ### 3\. Use for Research

In addition to the uses outlined above, by using zuuzs.com, you agree to allow us to anonymously use the information from you and your experiences to continue our consumer research objectives. The findings of our research may be sold to third parties or published in industry publications. However, such research will be conducted on an anonymous basis, and no Personal Information will be published or sold. This Privacy Policy does not limit our use or disclosure of any Anonymous Information in any way, and we reserve the right to use and disclose Anonymous Information to our partners, advertisers and other third parties in our discretion.

  4. ### 4\. Affiliated Companies

We may share some or all of your Personal Information with zuuzs.com affiliated companies that are under a common control, in which case we will require them to honor this Privacy Policy.

  5. ### 5\. Business Transfers

In the event we go through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Personal Information may be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any acquirer of ours or that acquirer’s assets may continue to process your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

  6. ### 6\. Disclosure of Anonymous Information to Trusted Third Parties By Us

We may share your Anonymous Information with third parties, but not in a manner that would reveal your identity. We may share your Personal Information, sometimes in conjunction with your Anonymous Information, with service providers that may be associated with us to perform functions on our behalf. For example, outsourced customer care agents or technology assistants may need access to your information to perform services for you. Your information will be treated as private and confidential by such service providers and not used for any other purpose than we authorize. In addition, from time to time, we may share Anonymous Information about our Member base with carefully selected third parties, so they can offer products and services that we believe may be of interest to our Members. 

  7. ### 7\. Disclosure to Trusted Third Parties at Your Request

While visiting zuuzs.com, we may provide you with advertisements, promotions, sweepstakes and offers from third party providers. If you choose to accept any such offers, you may either (depending on the situation) directly provide your information in connection with the offer to such third party provider, or we will provide your information, including billing information, to the third party provider by pre-populating the offer registration forms. Your information will not be transferred until you actually accept the offer. You may opt-out of the offer at any time up until your acceptance. Please refer to the third party provider’s own privacy policy (provided on the offer pages) if you have any questions regarding how your information is used by such providers. Please be aware that these offers may be presented on pages framed by zuuzs.com. Although these offer pages have the look and feel of zuuzs.com, you will be submitting your information directly to the third-party advertiser. You agree that we will not be responsible or liable for any loss or damage of any sort incurred as the result of any such dealings, including the sharing of the information you supply to us with third party providers described here, or as the result of the presence of such providers on zuuzs.com.

  8. ### 8\. Protection of zuuzs.com and Others

We release account and other Personal Information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms of Service and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of zuuzs.com, our Members, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing Personal Information from Members for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

## How We Keep Your Information Secure

The security of your Personal Information is important to zuuzs.com.  We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to help safeguard your Personal Information from unauthorized access and disclosure.  zuuzs.com uses a secure, encrypted connection (called an SSL connection) on all pages where you access or transmit Personal Information.  We want you to feel confident using zuuzs.com to transact business. However, no system can be completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your Personal Information, searches, or other communications will always remain secure.   It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.  Members should also take care with how they handle and disclose their Personal Information and should avoid sending Personal Information through insecure email.

## Your Privacy With zuuzs.com

zuuzs.com will never ask for your username, password or any other Personal Information in an unsolicited phone call, email or letter. Further, any contact with zuuzs.com customer service in which Personal Information is exchanged with a customer service representative will be used only for the purpose of satisfying your request. Any Personal Information you provide will not be recorded or used for any reason beyond that of the stated request.

If you choose to use our referral program to tell a friend about zuuzs.com, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend an email inviting him or her to visit zuuzs.com. zuuzs.com stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at contact@zuuzs.com to request that we remove this information from our database.

## Your Privacy with Our Affiliated Merchants and Advertisers

zuuzs.com does not record Personal Information passed from our Members to affiliated merchants. Order information, including order numbers and amounts, may be available to zuuzs.com, the affiliated merchant, or third party affiliate program management companies for accurate tracking purposes, but this information will not be released by zuuzs.com to other parties on a personally identifiable basis.  We may, however, aggregate this information on an anonymous basis to, among other things, perform market analysis and analyze trends.

## Links to or Access from Other Websites

zuuzs.com contains links to various other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites.  The ability to access information of third-parties from zuuzs.com, or links to other websites or locations, is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such third-parties, their products, their services, other websites, locations or their content.

We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices or the content of any other websites that may provide access to, or be linked to or from, zuuzs.com, including that of any social networking websites and third party advertisers whose offerings require you to navigate away from zuuzs.com.  These third-party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including Personal Information, from you and, in some instances, provide us with information about your activities on those websites.  We encourage our Members to read the privacy statements of each and every website they visit.  Each of these websites has a privacy policy that may differ from that of zuuzs.com. If you wish to receive special offers directly from a store, neither this Privacy Policy nor our opt-out policy applies to those communications. Instead, please refer to the relevant website’s privacy and opt-out policy.

You may be able to access your account or content of your account from third party websites, such as social networking websites, by way of various applications. The privacy policies and practices of such websites in connection with information you disclose on such websites may differ from the practices of zuuzs.com as set forth in this privacy statement, and you should review their policies and practices to ensure that the privacy of the information you submit on their website does not conflict with and is consistent with how you wish your information to be treated. 

## Your Choices and Responsibilities

We offer you choices regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your Personal Information.  You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of zuuzs.com because such information may be required in order for you to register as a Member; purchase products or services; participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes; ask a question; or initiate other transactions on zuuzs.com. 

As a Member, you have certain obligations to other Members. Some of these obligations are imposed by applicable law and regulations, and others have become commonplace in communities of like-minded Members such as zuuzs.com: 

  1. You must, at all times, abide by the terms and conditions of the then-current Privacy Policy and Terms of Service. This includes respecting all intellectual property rights that may belong to third parties (such as trademarks or photographs). 
  2. You must not download or otherwise disseminate any information that may be deemed to be injurious, violent, offensive, racist or xenophobic, or which may otherwise violate the purpose and spirit of zuuzs.com and its community of Members. 
  3. You must keep your username and password confidential and not share it with others. 

Any violation of these guidelines may lead to the restriction, suspension or termination of your account at the sole discretion of zuuzs.com.

You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes. When you receive promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further promotional communications from us and you will have the opportunity to “opt-out” by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the promotional e-mail you receive or by contacting us directly at contact@zuuzs.com.

Despite your indicated email marketing preferences, we may send you administrative emails regarding zuuzs.com, including, for example, administrative and transactional confirmations, and notices of updates to our Privacy Policy if we choose to provide such notices to you in this manner.

You have the right to request a copy of the Personal Information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your Personal Information, please contact us at contact@zuuzs.com. We may charge a reasonable fee for this service. We want to make sure that your information is accurate and up-to-date. You may ask us to correct or remove information which you think is inaccurate. You may change any of your profile information by editing it in the profile settings page.

It is the Member's responsibility to update and maintain accurate contact information in their account. You can make changes by visiting your account page and entering corrections. Email and street addresses that are entered into a Member's personal profile page are the addresses that will be used for all contact including for your fundzs payments. zuuzs.com is not responsible for payments sent to an incorrect addresses provided by you.

We will post all changes to this Privacy Policy here at zuuzs.com. You are responsible for checking periodically on policy updates.

## How You Can Access Your Information

If you have an online account with us, you have the ability to review and update your Personal Information online by logging into your account and clicking on your account settings. More information about how to contact us is provided below. If you have an online account with us, you also may close your account at any time by editing the profile settings for your account. After you close your account, you will not be able to sign in to zuuzs.com or access any of your Personal Information. However, you can re-activate your previous account by following instructions we will give you at the time you close your account. If you close your account, we may still retain certain information associated with your account for analytical purposes and recordkeeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, enforce our terms and conditions, take actions we deem necessary to protect the integrity of zuuzs.com or our Members, or take other actions otherwise permitted by law. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties' policies. 

## Opt-Out

You may use the following options for removing your information from our e-mail database if you wish to opt out of receiving promotional e-mails and newsletters.

  * Click on the “unsubscribe” link on the bottom of the e-mail;
  * Send mail to the following postal address letting us know which promotional e-mails you wish to opt-out of: 

zuuzs, LLC  
P.O. Box 631155  
Irving, TX 75063-1155

It may take up to 10 days for us to process an opt-out request.  We may send you other types of transactional and relationship email communications, such as service announcements, administrative notices, and surveys, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. Please note that changing information in your account, or otherwise opting out of receipt of promotional email communications will only affect future activities or communications from us. If we have already provided your information to a third party (such as a service provider) before you have changed your preferences or updated your information, you may have to change you preferences directly with that third party.

## Visiting Our Website From Outside the United States 

This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on zuuzs.com from residents of the United States. If you are visiting zuuzs.com from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy. 

## Children's Privacy

Although zuuzs.com is a general audience website, we restrict the use of our service to individuals age 18 and above. Children under the age of 18 are not permitted to use zuuzs.com.  Furthermore, we do not intentionally collect or maintain Personal Information from those who are under 13 years old.  Protecting the privacy of children is very important to us. If we obtain actual knowledge that a Member is under 13, we will take steps to remove that Member's Personal Information permanently from our databases in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. By using zuuzs.com, you are representing that you are at least 18 years old. 

## Feedback

If you provide feedback to us, we may use and disclose such feedback for any purpose, provided we do not associate such feedback with your Personal Information. We will collect any information contained in such feedback and will treat the Personal Information in it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You agree that any such comments and any email we receive becomes our property. We may use feedback for marketing purposes or to add to or modify our services without paying any royalties or other compensation to you.

## No Rights of Third Parties

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any Personal Information relating to Members of the website. 

## Acceptance of Privacy Policy

Your use of zuuzs.com, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and the applicable Terms of Service.  BY USING ZUUZS.COM, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES SET OUT IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE APPLICABLE Terms of Service.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the “last updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy page and any other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, or by other means, such as e-mail, at our discretion.

If you object to any such changes, you must cease using zuuzs.com.  Your continued use of any portion of zuuzs.com following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes. 

## How to Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information-handling practices, or if you would like to request information about our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes, please contact us by email or postal mail as follows: 

zuuzs, LLC   
PO Box 631155  
Irving, TX 75063-1155  
contact@zuuzs.com 

_Last Updated on August 15, 2011_
